[

](https://www.rigidlifelines.com/)

[

](https://www.rigidlifelines.com/)

MENUMENU

[Home](https://www.rigidlifelines.com/) » Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this policy so that you can understand how we collect, use, communicate, disclose, and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.

* Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
* We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
* We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
* Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and—to the extent necessary for those purposes—should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
* We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use, or modification.
* We will information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information readily available to customers.
* We will not sell or give away names, mailing addresses, telephone numbers, email addresses, credit card information, or any other personally-identifiable information to anyone.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

### Explore Rigid Lifelines

### Let us help you

Contact us today to find the perfect product fit for your job

604 Hemlock Rd  
Morgantown, PA 19543

**call us at:**  
(800) 869-2080

### Newsletter Signup

* Email

Δ

###### Product Categories

###### Products by Industry

### Info Box

© Rigid Lifelines is a division of [SPANCO, inc.](https://www.spanco.com/)
